Mss.Rec.53 Mss.Rec.53
American Philosophical Society
Wenathcee language recordings
1965
Mss.Rec.53
American Philosophical Society
6.0 Reel(s)
Linguistic field recordings of elicited vocabulary, pronunciation, and some grammar in the Columbia-Wenatchi language, often referred to on the recording as Moses. Includes occasional vocabulary in the Colville dialect of the Okanagan language. Recorded near in the Methow Valley south of Carlton, Washington, in June - August 1965.
6 sound tape reels (7 hr., 44 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 2 track, mono; 5 in. and 7 in.
Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-
Miller, Agnes
Miller, Jerome
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Presented by M. Dale Kinkade in 1966. This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Columbia-Wenatchi language; Colville dialect; Indians of North America--Washington (State); Okanagan language; Sound recordings; Washington (State)--Languages
- Audio recordings
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-06-17; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:15:42; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
    Scope and Contents note
    Elicited vocabulary in the Columbia-Wenatchi language--often referred to on the recording as Moses--with occasional vocabulary in the Colville dialect of the Okanagan language. Recorded in the Methow Valley, south of Carlton, Washington.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Sound tape reel) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Columbia-Wenatchi language; Colville dialect; Okanagan language; Okanogan County (Wash.); Washington (State)--Languages
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-06-19; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:15:26; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-06-23; 01-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:14:46; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-06-26; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:23:34; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-06-30; 02-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:28:09; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-02; 02-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:21:11; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-02; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:13:16; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-07; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:22:09; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-10; 03-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:20:21; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-14; 03-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:27:17; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-17; 03-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:26; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
    Elicited vocabulary in the Columbia-Wenatchi language, often referred to on the recording as Moses. Recorded in the Methow Valley, south of Carlton, Washington.
    Columbia-Wenatchi language; Okanogan County (Wash.); Washington (State)--Languages
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-17; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:10:32; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
    Elicited vocabulary in the Columbia-Wenatchi language--often referred to on the recording as Moses--with occasional vocabulary in the Colville dialect of Okanagan. Recorded in the Methow Valley, south of Carlton, Washington.
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-24; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:30:44; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-07-28; 04-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:30:49; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-08-02; 04-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:20:23; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-08-04; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:37:26; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
    Columbia-Wenatchi language; Colville dialect; Okanagan language--Glossaries, vocabularies, etc.; Okanogan County (Wash.); Washington (State)--Languages
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-08-06; 05-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:28:18; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-08-11; 05-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:29:59; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-08-13; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:28:05; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome
  - Wenatchee Language Vocabulary, 1965-08-18; 06-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:33:10; Kinkade, M. Dale (Marvin Dale), 1933-; Miller, Agnes; Miller, Jerome